hi I am Rachel yoga and I am a mother to
a three year old baby girl currently I
work as a radio resident in the public
hospital and that means we are in charge
of the Imaging's of a certain patient
from x-rays ultrasound CT scans and MRIs
during the ECT you not much has changed
in terms of that we still go on duties
and we still handle patients as a
second-year I am mostly in charge of the
ultrasound modality which means I have
close patient interaction so it really
doesn't matter if it's a clean patient
as we call it or a cognate suspect
patient we still have to do the
ultrasound nonetheless so when it comes
to doing an ultrasound for called the
patient we just make sure that we use
proper PPE or the personal protective
equipment so that we can protect
ourselves my fear mostly is that I might
bring home the virus because I still
come home after duties and I spend time
with my husband and my daughter and it
scares me that they're here safe at home
but because of the job that I do and
because of the exposure that I might get
that they can get the virus as well as
for sacrifices I think the major one
would be time if I happen to be on duty
for a certain holiday or a certain
family birthday or event then that's
something I would have to sacrifice
given all the sacrifices and the fears
that come with the job I still continue
to do it because this is my calling and
it is one way to help people and I also
want to be a good role model to my my
daughter and show her that in times of a
crisis people will still be willing to
help and people will still be doing
their duties and that you can always
depend on
and I want my daughter to feel that way
towards her mother someone who she can
depend on on whatever and whenever
[Music]